William Carey Crane papers, Inclusive: 1809-1944, Bulk: 1834-1885
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
William Carey Crane papers
Inclusive: 1809-1944, Bulk: 1834-1885
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
68
Crane, William Carey, 1816 - 1885
46 document boxes and 1 oversized box.
The William Carey Crane papers contain personal correspondence, financial documents, legal documents, literary productions, and photographic materials belonging to the former president of Baylor University.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Scope and Content
The William Carey Crane papers being in 1809 and end in 1944, but the bulk of the materials originated during William Carey Crane’s prestigious career as pastor and educator (1834-1885). Many materials are general correspondence and literary productions, but the collection also includes personal correspondence, family correspondence, legal documents, financial documents, and photographic materials.
Arrangement
The current organization of the William Carey Crane papers has gone through significant changes prior to this finding aid. Currently the records are arranged in seven series: I. General Correspondence, II. Personal Correspondence, III. Family Correspondence, IV. Legal Documents, V. Financial Documents, VI. Literary Productions, and VII. Photographic Materials. Series I and VI comprise the bulk of the collection.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 68. Acquired 0-00-00
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Burleson, Rufus Columbus, 1823-1901.; Crane, William Carey, 1816-1885.
Subjects (Organizations)
Baptist General Convention of Texas.; Baylor University -- History.
Subjects
Baptists -- Sermons.; Baptists -- Texas -- Clergy.
Genres
Certificates.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Deeds.; Diaries.; Financial records.; Financial statements.; Lectures.; Minutes (Records); Pamphlets.; Periodicals.; Photographs.; Programs.; Records and briefs.; Reports.; Scrapbooks.; Speeches.; Transcriptions (documents).
- General Correspondence, 1832-1885, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Average.
  Biography/Profile
  This series, the largest in the collection, contains William Carey Crane’s correspondence about Baylor University, the Civil War, and Baptists in Texas.
  - General, 1832-1835 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General, 1836-1837 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General, 1838 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General, 1839 January-April 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General, 1839 April 18-June 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General, 1839 June 17-September 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - General, 1839 September 7-October 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General, 1839 October 23-1840 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General, 1840 January 25-March 9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - General, 1840 March 25-April (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - General, 1840 May (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - General, 1840 June-August 3 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - General, 1840 August 15-September 12 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - General, 1840 September 14-October 25 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General, 1840 October 27-December 6 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - General, 1840 December 12-1841 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General, 1841 January 23-March 18 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - General, 1841 March 24-April (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - General, 1841 May-June 6 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - General, 1841 June 8-28 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - General, 1841 July-August 7 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - General, 1841 August 10-November 4 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - General, 1841 November 8-December 16 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - General, 1841 December 28-1842 January (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - General, 1842 February-April (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - General, 1842 May (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - General, 1842 July-October (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - General, 1842 November-December (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - General, 1843 January (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - General, 1843 February-May (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - General, 1843 June-November (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - General, 1844 February-June (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General, 1844 July (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General, 1844 August-October 17 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - General, 1844 October 21-November 4 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - General, 1844 November 15-30 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - General, 1844 December-1845 January (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - General, 1845 February-April (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - General, 1845 May-June 14 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - General, 1845 June 16-July (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - General, 1845 August 3-16 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - General, 1845 August 21-September (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - General, 1845 October-December 16 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - General, 1845 December 18-1846 February 11 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - General, 1846 February 12-March (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - General, 1846 April 2-16 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - General, 1846 April 23-June (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - General, 1846 July-August 16 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - General, 1846 August 26-September (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - General, 1846 October-November (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - General, 1846 December 1-26 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - General, 1846 December 30-1847 January 23 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - General, 1847 January 24-February (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - General, 1847 March (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - General, 1847 April-May 6 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - General, 1847 May 11-June 11 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - General, 1847 June 21-July 17 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - General, 1847 July 19-August 10 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - General, 1847 August 13-September (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - General, 1847 October-November 13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - General, 1847 November 19-December 7 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - General, 1847 December 11-28 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - General, 1848 January 4-24 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - General, 1848 January 26-February 25 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - General, 1848 February 28-March 14 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - General, 1848 March 15-April 19 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - General, 1848 April 20-May 17 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - General, 1848 May 24-July (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - General, 1848 August-September 7 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - General, 1848 September 12-October 21 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - General, 1848 October 22-December 6 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - General, 1848 December 7-20 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - General, 1848 December 21-1849 January 3 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - General, 1849 January 4-February 15 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - General, 1849 February 16-28 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - General, 1849 March (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - General, 1849 April (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - General, 1849 May-June 13 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - General, 1849 June 14-July 18 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - General, 1849 July 24-September 10 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - General, 1849 September 25-October (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - General, 1849 November (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - General, 1849 December-1850 January 10 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - General, 1850 January 21-February 15 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - General, 1850 February 25-March 16 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - General, 1850 March 19-April 10 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - General, 1850 April 13-May 18 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - General, 1850 May 20-June 15 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - General, 1850 June 19-August 3 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - General, 1850 August 10-September (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - General, 1850 October-November 18 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - General, 1850 November 27-December (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - General, 1851 January-March 6 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - General, 1851 March 10-April (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - General, 1851 May-June (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - General, 1851 July-August (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - General, 1851 September-October 17 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - General, 1851 October 20-November 11 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - General, 1851 November 14-December 9 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - General, 1851 December 14-1852 January 16 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - General, 1852 January 20-February 6 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - General, 1852 February 8-March 3 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - General, 1852 March 6-29 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - General, 1852 April-May 12 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - General, 1852 May 19-July 6 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - General, 1852 July 7-August 15 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - General, 1852 August 18-September (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - General, 1852 October 4-26 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - General, 1852 October 28-December 3 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - General, 1852 December 16-1853 January 24 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - General, 1853 January 28-March 11 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - General, 1853 March 19-May 11 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - General, 1853 May 11-June 22 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - General, 1853 June 22-July 11 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - General, 1853 July 16-August 15 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - General, 1853 August 19-September 7 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - General, 1853 September 9-27 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - General, 1853 September 28-October (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - General, 1853 November-December (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - General, 1854 January-February 14 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - General, 1854 February 15-March 8 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - General, 1854 March 14-April 27 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - General, 1854 April 28-May 29 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - General, 1854 May 30-June 24 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - General, 1854 June 24-July 27 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - General, 1854 July 29-August 17 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - General, 1854 August 18-September 12 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - General, 1854 September 13-25 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - General, 1854 September 26-October 17 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - General, 1854 October 20-November 8 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - General, 1854 November 12-December 11 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - General, 1854 December 15-1855 January 6 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - General, 1855 January 8-February 8 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - General, 1855 February 11-March 4 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - General, 1855 March 4-20 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - General, 1855 March 20-April 23 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - General, 1855 April 25-June 5 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - General, 1855 June 5-July 26 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - General, 1855 July 27-August 14 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - General, 1855 August 17-September 3 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - General, 1855 September 4-17 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - General, 1855 September 24-October 25 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - General, 1855 October 28-November 24 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - General, 1855 November 24-December (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - General, 1856 January 2-24 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - General, 1856 January 26-February 22 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - General, 1856 February 25-March 18 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - General, 1856 March 21-May 3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - General, 1856 May 5-June 9 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - General, 1856 June 11-28 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - General, 1856 July-August 8 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - General, 1856 August 13-September (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - General, 1856 October (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - General, 1856 November (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - General, 1856 December (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - General, 1857 January (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - General, 1857 February-March 6 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - General, 1857 March 8-April 16 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - General, 1857 April 17-May 13 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - General, 1857 May 15-June (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - General, 1857 July-August 20 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - General, 1857 August 22-September 14 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - General, 1857 September 15-October (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - General, 1857 November-December 6 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - General, 1857 December 10-1858 January 11 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - General, 1858 January 13-February 4 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - General, 1858 February 8-March 18 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - General, 1858 March 20-April 3 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - General, 1858 April 5-20 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - General, 1858 April 22-May 12 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - General, 1858 May 13-June 5 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - General, 1858 June 8-July 8 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - General, 1858 July-August 8 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - General, 1858 August 12-September 15 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - General, 1858 September 16-October 15 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - General, 1858 October 18-November (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - General, 1858 December 3-20 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - General, 1858 December 20-1859 January 15 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - General, 1859 January 17-February 8 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - General, 1859 February 8-25 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - General, 1859 March (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - General, 1859 April 2-23 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - General, 1859 April 25-June 7 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - General, 1859 June 8-29 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - General, 1859 July (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - General, 1859 August 1-18 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - General, 1859 August 23-September 14 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - General, 1859 September 15-27 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - General, 1859 September 29-October (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - General, 1859 November 2-21 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - General, 1859 November 23-December 14 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - General, 1859 December 16-1860 February 8 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - General, 1860 February 10-March 6 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - General, 1860 March 6-24 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - General, 1860 March 26-April 10 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - General, 1860 April 11-May 4 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - General, 1860 May 8-31 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - General, 1860 June 1-18 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - General, 1860 June 19-July 12 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - General, 1860 July 15-August 21 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - General, 1860 August 22-September 24 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - General, 1860 September 26-October (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - General, 1860 November-December 18 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - General, 1860 December 20-27 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - General, 1861 January-February 23 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - General, 1861 February 24-March 20 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - General, 1861 March 20-April 5 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - General, 1861 April 6-June (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - General, 1861 July-August 22 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - General, 1861 August 24-October 21 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - General, 1861 October 23-December 8 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - General, 1861 December 9-1862 January (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - General, 1862 February-March (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - General, 1862 April-June (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - General, 1862 July-September (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - General, 1862 October-1863 February (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - General, 1863 April-August (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - General, 1864 January-February (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - General, 1864 March-June (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - General, 1864 July-August 11 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - General, 1864 August 13-25 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - General, 1864 September-October (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - General, 1864 November-December 5 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - General, 1864 December 16-1865 January 6 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - General, 1865 January 8-21 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - General, 1865 January 28-February 15 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - General, 1865 February 16-March 12 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - General, 1865 March 13-April 7 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - General, 1865 April 9-30 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - General, 1865 May (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - General, 1865 June 1-27 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - General, 1865 June 27-August 4 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - General, 1865 August 8-October 14 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - General, 1865 October 16-30 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - General, 1865 November-December 12 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - General, 1865 December 13-1866 January (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - General, 1866 February-March 1 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - General, 1866 March 2-22 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - General, 1866 March 24-April 17 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - General, 1866 April 18-May (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - General, 1866 June-July 15 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - General, 1866 July 16-August 24 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - General, 1866 August 25-September 14 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - General, 1866 September 15-October 3 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - General, 1866 October 5-31 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - General, 1866 November (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - General, 1866 December (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - General, 1867 January 2-20 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - General, 1867 January 22-February 15 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - General, 1867 February 18-March 7 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - General, 1867 March 9-23 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - General, 1867 March 24-31 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - General, 1867 April 1-21 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - General, 1867 April 24-May 24 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - General, 1867 May 28-June 24 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - General, 1867 June 25-July 22 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - General, 1867 July 24-August (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - General, 1867 September 1-16 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - General, 1867 September 18-October (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - General, 1867 November-December 2 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - General, 1867 December 3-1868 January 18 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - General, 1868 January 18-February 18 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - General, 1868 February 19-March 14 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - General, 1868 March 20-April (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - General, 1868 May 4-26 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - General, 1868 May 30-July 23 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - General, 1868 July 24-September (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - General, 1868 October (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - General, 1868 November (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - General, 1868 December (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - General, 1869 January 5-14 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - General, 1869 January 18-23 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - General, 1869 January 25-February 8 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - General, 1869 February 9-March 12 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - General, 1869 March 12-30 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - General, 1869 April 2-16 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - General, 1869 April 19-May 17 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - General, 1869 May 18-June 12 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - General, 1869 June 14-July 3 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - General, 1869 July 3-August 13 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - General, 1869 August 14-September 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - General, 1869 September 3-October 19 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - General, 1869 October 21-December 4 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - General, 1869 December 7-23 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - General, 1869 December 26-1870 January 15 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - General, 1870 January 16-February 7 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - General, 1870 February 8-March 4 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - General, 1870 March 5-31 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - General, 1870 April-May 25 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - General, 1870 May 26-July 21 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - General, 1870 July 21-August (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - General, 1870 September (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - General, 1870 October (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - General, 1870 November 1-17 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - General, 1870 November 21-December 14 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - General, 1870 December 15-1871 January 9 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - General, 1870 January 10-February 13 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - General, 1871 February 14-March 3 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - General, 1871 March 3-April 10 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - General, 1871 April 10-May 9 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - General, 1871 May 15-June 17 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - General, 1871 June 19-July (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - General, 1871 August 2-25 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - General, 1871 August 26-September 15 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - General, 1871 September 15-October 14 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - General, 1871 October 15-23 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - General, 1871 October 24-November 3 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - General, 1871 November 4-20 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - General, 1871 November 23-December 11 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - General, 1871 December 15-1872 January 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - General, 1872 January 2-14 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - General, 1872 January 15-February 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - General, 1872 February 6-19 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - General, 1872 February 21-29 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - General, 1872 March 1-16 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - General, 1872 March 18-April 8 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - General, 1872 April 10-29 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - General, 1872 May-June 10 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - General, 1872 June 11-30 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - General, 1872 July 2-23 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - General, 1872 July 23-August 14 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - General, 1872 August 15-31 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - General, 1872 September 1-16 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - General, 1872 September 17-October 4 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - General, 1872 October 5-29 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - General, 1872 November 2-15 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - General, 1872 November 15-December 2 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - General, 1872 December 2-16 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - General, 1872 December 18-31 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - General, 1873 January 1-6 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - General, 1873 January 6-29 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - General, 1873 January 30-February 12 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - General, 1873 February 13-25 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - General, 1873 March 1-22 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - General, 1873 March 22-April 9 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - General, 1873 April 11-30 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - General, 1873 May 1-22 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - General, 1873 May 22-June5 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - General, 1873 June 6-18 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - General, 1873 June 21-July 11 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - General, 1873 July 12-26 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - General, 1873 July 28-August 8 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - General, 1873 August 9-25 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - General, 1873 August 26-September 12 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - General, 1873 September 13-October 8 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - General, 1873 October 8-31 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - General, 1873 November-December 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - General, 1873 December 3-15 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - General, 1873 December 15-30 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - General, 1874 January 1-15 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - General, 1874 January 17-February 3 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - General, 1874 February 4-17 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - General, 1874 February 18-March 18 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - General, 1874 March 19-April 2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - General, 1874 April 2-27 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - General, 1874 May (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - General, 1874 June (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - General, 1874 July 1-27 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - General, 1874 July 27-August 18 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - General, 1874 August 19-September 10 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - General, 1874 September 14-25 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - General, 1874 September 25-October 16 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - General, 1874 October 17-November 11 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - General, 1874 November 13-December 3 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - General, 1874 December 5-26 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - General, 1874 December 26-1875 January 4 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - General, 1875 January 5-23 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - General, 1875 January 23-February 3 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - General, 1875 February 6-25 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - General, 1875 March 1-23 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - General, 1875 March 23-April 17 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - General, 1875 April 19-30 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - General, 1875 May 2-21 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - General, 1875 May 25-June 8 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - General, 1875 June 8-July 8 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - General, 1875 July 9-31 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - General, 1875 August 4-22 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - General, 1875 August 23-September 3 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - General, 1875 September 3-28 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - General, 1875 September 29-October 20 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - General, 1875 October 23-November 9 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - General, 1875 November 9-December 14 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - General, 1875 December 14-1876 January 10 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - General, 1876 January 10-20 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - General, 1876 January 21-February (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - General, 1876 March 4-April 5 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - General, 1876 April 5-May 8 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - General, 1876 May 13-June 6 (Box 16, Folder 7)